# Hyungrok Kim

https://rokrokss.com

: https://github.com/q0115643

**t**: +821089595643

e: hyungrok.kim@kaist.ac.kr

## **PROFILE**

I am working for PUBG as a Platform Engineer.

Belonged in Industrial Design department for 2 years, moved to Computer Science 2 years ago. Studied Data Science and NLP trying to understand the linguistic communication of emotions. Currently interested in Microservice Architecture, studying to become a expert platform engineer.

## **WORK EXPERIENCES**

#### **PUBG**

**Platform Engineer** 

Jul 2019 - Present

Seoul, Republic of Korea

UILAB(http://uilab.kr/)

**Undergraduate Researcher** 

Study on Metaphor Comperhension

Jul 2018 - Dec 2018

Dajeon, Republic of Korea

## **ORGANIZATION**

#### Korea Design Membership(http://kidp.or.kr)

Attend various design classes

Mar 2016 - Feb 2018

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology**

B.S. in Computer Science Minor in Industrial Design

Mar 2014 - Present

Daejeon, Korea

## **CORSEWORKS**

#### **CS Major**

CS574 Natural Language Processing

CS570 Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning

CS492 Introduction to Machine Learning

CS474 Text Mining

CS470 Introduction to Artificial Intelligence

CS330 Operating Systems and Lab

CS320 Programming Language

CS311 Computer Organization

CS230 System Programming

CS204 Discrete Mathematics

CS206 Data Structure

ID217 Presentation Technique CS300 Introduction to Algorithms

**ID218 Photo Techniques** 

ID307 Interface Design

ID302 Space Design

**ID220 Interaction Prototyping** 

ID301 Product Design Factors

ID219 Computer-Aided Design

ID214 Digital Design Graphics

Others

ID215 Introduction to Industrial Design MAS109 Introduction to Linear Algebra

ID213 Product Design Fundamentals

ID212 Three-Dimensional Design

MAS205 Probability and Statistics

## **PROJECTS**

#### **REST Countries**

https://naranara.net

Simple react webpage of listing various country information.

React, Redux, Typescript, Webpack, Babel, Sass May 2019

#### **Arithmetic Hash**



Build LSTM-based query encoder designed to replace the hash algorithm of p2p network

Pytorch, RNN, Markov Model Jan 2019

### **GCN-RNNG** based Korean NMT







Pytorch, SyntaxNet, GCN, RNNG, KoNLPy, Word2Vec May 2018 - Aug 2018

#### **Neural Poetry Scansion**



Based on Original Paper (Proceedings of AAAI 2016) deep-learning apporach to improve performance on poety-analysis

Pytorch, BiLSTM-CRF, Word2Vec

May 2018 - Aug 2018

#### HarmonyTable



Hardware project of combining harmony & turntable in Interaction Prototyping

Arduino

Sep 2016 - Oct 2016

#### **FlyDuck**





Tangible Interface Game

Processing, Arduino

Nov 2016 - Dec 2016